A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Hey, Sid. Are you going to be all right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I should have tried to help you escape too, Lord Death, but the distance was too great.
No, no excuses. I have failed you.
No, no. You made the best decision given the circumstances.
Still, I can't believe it. Our own Dr. Medusa was a witch this whole time.
She was using soul protect. It's the only way she could have hidden from us.
Lord Death, aren't there any techniques we can use to combat the soul protect move?
Kill it.
If not, then we're basically helpless. How can you fight what you can't see?
Our struggle against witches has been going on for centuries.
Over the years, witches have come up with any number of new spells.
But for every new spell, maesters and weapons have developed new ways of countering them.
For instance, in order to detect and hunt down witches,
maesters were born who had the ability to send souls.
But now the witches can counter them by using soul protect.
So what we have to do now is develop a new technique.
The only way to do that now is to quiche your eyes.
What?
I suppose there's no point in hiding it anymore.
If you shut the lid on something that stinks,
all you're really doing is hiding the bad smell.
To get rid of it, you have to open the lid back up and dive in.
Okay, everyone.
Could I have your attention for a moment?
There's a kishin sleeping underneath the DWMA.
Uh, I think they may need more than that.
I think they may need more than that.
To get rid of it, I think they may need more than that.
It all happened before this academy was created.
I'll begin at the beginning.
This is the story of a man.
His name was Asherah.
Asherah kept himself covered,
wrapping his face in long scarves
and layering five shirts on top of each other.
He wasn't very good at trusting other people.
He didn't confide in anybody.
He was basically a big ball of paranoia wrapped up in a dozen scarves.
Tell me what happened with the Eastern Witches.
Sir, by the time we arrived,
Asherah had slaughtered them all.
Asherah was a member of my personal squad.
He was by far the best and strongest of all the eight guardians.
However, he was also the most frightening one of them all.
Always terrified of something.
Asherah became obsessed with power.
Eventually, he broke our most sacred rule
and began collecting the souls of humans.
And thus, because of him,
it was born.
The Kishan.
The source of all madness.
Hold on.
I thought only weapons could consume souls.
How was Asherah able to eat them?
I told you, he was a frightened man.
He was terrified of his partner as well.
So, he ate his own weapon.
What?
How is something like that even possible?
You know,
now that I think about it,
I'm not sure he was ever human to begin with.
It's possible he's nothing more than the embodiment
of something that lies deep within his heart.
Fear, for example.
The underground battle commences.
Break through Medusa's vector arrow?
Hey, kid.
How did Lord Death seal away this Asherah guy in the first place?
My father tore off Asherah's skin,
made a tightly sealed bag out of it,
and stuffed Asherah inside.
Then he rooted his own soul and body
here inside Death City
to keep the Kishan from ever breaking free.
And because of that,
Lord Death can never leave the city?
What if the seal was broken
and the Kishan managed to get free?
Would Lord Death be able to go wherever he wanted?
That wouldn't work.
Lord Death has attached his soul to this town.
I suppose you could even say
he's become one with Death City.
So it's like he's trapped inside himself.
If he wanted to go somewhere,
he'd have to find a way of giving the city legs.
And I don't really see that happening anytime soon,
do you?
Uh-uh.
You can't even imagine how disastrous things will be
if the Kishan is revived.
It's madness is like a plague.
Also, you should know you can't control it.
Hell is something you carry around with you.
Right inside your weak, flimsy little head.
Now come along.
Magnus is waiting for you.
There's no escape.
You're like a needle stuck in the grooves of the record
spinning around and around.
Yeah, right.
Screw that.
Your analogy isn't persuasive.
I mean, look at that needle.
It's jumping around all over the place.
I'm waiting for your decision.
What's it gonna be, soul?
Ah!
The city sure is lively.
They really know how to throw a party.
I wanted to go too,
but they said only Academy students were allowed
with their fancy gala.
No fair.
Oh, I don't have a job,
so I don't have any money to go shopping.
There's no choice.
I'll just have to go visit this shop guy.
He knows me,
so he'll give me something at least.
Blair, is that you?
Hi, fish shop guy.
Blair, here you go.
I saved this fish just for you.
Oh, no, fish shop guy!
I would do something like this.
What's that?
I'll have to take care of those cheeky rats.
It took me forever
to find that free source of food.
I'll have to take care of those cheeky rats.
We've gone a pretty long way now.
Hey, Maka,
can you sense any witches up ahead
with that little gift of yours?
Their soul protects are probably on right now.
Oh, all right.
That's lame.
Sensing stuff's the only thing you're half decent at.
You don't even know how to piss me off.
What? What?
Professor Stein!
Yeah?
I've got something.
It's a soul just beyond those shadows.
There's someone there.
I know that soul.
I'm sure of it.
That nasty, despicable feeling.
Papa.
I'm not nasty.
You're despicable.
How did you manage to escape
from the trap they set up there?
When it comes to chasing a woman,
no one's faster than I am.
I should have guessed.
It is a relief to see you, though.
I wasn't sure how much I'd be able to do
without my weapon around.
What do we got?
Are they up ahead?
Uh-huh.
Lying in wait for us.
Listen up.
From this point forward,
there's no telling what could happen.
It'd be best for you weapons
not to return to human form
during the battle.
When you're vulnerable,
a single blow could be the end of you.
Right.
Okay.
Why are they sitting up there
waiting for us?
I thought they were on their way
to the Kishin.
No.
They would have left some behind
for protection.
Hey, did you hear something?
Hear what?
Yeah, I heard that.
It sounds like footsteps to me.
So they're finally showing themselves.
Who's it gonna be?
Someone able to defend against
and defeat multiple opponents.
Someone who can attack
several people simultaneously.
Someone who will make absolutely sure
not to let us through
no matter what.
How lovely to see you all again.
All right.
Here's how I think
it's going to break down.
For the most part,
we can anticipate
our enemy's moves.
The first roadblock
is going to be Medusa.
The demon sword
will be the second barrier.
After that,
the remaining two
will be making their way
to the Kishin.
The werewolf Maka
and the others fought before
is immortal,
so he'll be in charge
of protecting the black blood
at all costs.
Now then,
this is what we will do.
I'll stay here
and keep Medusa busy.
While I'm distracting her,
I want the three of you
to run past her
as quickly as possible.
Kid,
you're the most mobile
of our little army,
so you continue on ahead of us
after the two
who are heading
for the Kishin.
Understood.
Blackstar,
you'll be keeping
the demon sword busy
so Kid and Maka
can get through.
Since you can attack
directly with your
soul wavelength,
you can do the most damage
to the demon sword.
Yeah.
Finally, Maka,
you run on past Medusa
and the demon sword
to catch up with Kid.
Then you destroy
the black blood.
Right.
There's just one last thing.
I want you all
to make me a promise.
I want you to promise
not to die.
Can you do that?
Yes, sir.
Holding a strategy meeting
right in front of your enemy?
Is that really
the best idea?
Ah, well,
I guess we'll just have
to take our chances,
won't we?
Always so stupidly confident,
aren't you?
Shall we start
the party then?
Nick, snake,
Cobra, Cobra.
Here we go.
Don't worry about
getting past her
right away.
Wait for a good opening
to present itself.
Stay calm
and collected.
Here goes.
Vector arrow.
Times three.
She's picked a perfect spell
for keeping multiple
attackers at bay.
And it's more powerful
than last time.
If you get scared,
go to sleep.
Yeah, okay.
I'm not gonna hold back.
Now.
It's Annie's sword roll.
Wait.
It's time to punish you,
impudent boy.
Death slide.
We're through.
Maka, Blackstar,
I'm going to keep moving.
You're blocking.
Right.
Why, you.
Yahoo!
Two of them made it through.
Enchant sword mode,
off.
We've got somewhere to be.
Maka,
hurry up and go after them.
Yeah.
All vectors to Maka.
I remember this.
I've seen how this spell
works once before.
So I already know
the path that I have to take.
Right down the middle.
The vector arrows
radiate from their
power source, Medusa.
If Maka is going
to get past them,
her best bet
is to go through
the gap in between.
But in that position,
she'll be surrounded
by the arrows.
A moment of hesitation
and she could die.
And if Maka doesn't get there
before the arrows close in,
she won't have a chance.
Focus on your speed, Maka.
I have to run faster!
Think you can't be afraid
of what you can't see, huh?
The arrows sound close.
Maka!
Damn it.
Of course I'm imagining
the worst.
Now the fear is beginning
to weigh down my legs.
No.
The fear should make me
run faster.
Faster!
You aren't going to beat me!
You aren't going anywhere, girl!
Nice try!
Stop!
Soul Force!
It's just you and me now, Medusa.
Good.
Let's keep going.
Yeah.
I miscalculated
to think that I let
all three of them get away.
But as long as I stop you
from getting any further,
my plan will still succeed.
Those three are just children.
They should be taken care of
quickly enough.
I wouldn't underestimate
those children.
Didn't you learn anything
about our students' abilities
during your little stint
at the academy?
Or are you just a fool?
No, I think you're the fool.
We'll see.
I wonder how they're going
to do against
the demon sword.
Hey, did something
with four wheels,
two legs, and two arms
just blow past us?
Medusa!
I must admit,
I always loved seeing you
in your nurse's outfit.
Although, the thought
of seeing you out of it
is more exciting,
especially if I was
taking it off.
You know, I was dancing
with her tonight.
Yeah, I saw that.
Just rub it in,
why don't you?
Boys, boys,
must you fight?
It embarrasses me so.
Does it?
How impolite of us.
My, my.
That's quite a large soul
you have.
Perhaps I would be willing
to dance with you again.
Thanks, but I'm gonna
pass on that one.
I don't think you're really
fit for dancing now.
My feet.
What is this?
Those are soul thread sutures.
The soul wavelength
I blasted into you
a second ago
is still there.
As we speak,
it's working its way
through your body
like an electric charge.
I use the wavelength
like a thread
to sew your feet
to the ground.
How can you control
your soul wavelength
that precisely?
A weapon can have
more than one use.
He doesn't just amplify
a Meister's wavelength.
It's also possible
to increase the accuracy
of wavelength control.
So then it's a technique
that only powerful Meisters
and weapons can pull off.
Medusa,
listen closely
to what I have to say.
I'm the only death scythe
at the DWMA.
If I allow the Kishin
to revive under my watch,
I won't be able
to show my face
to any of the other
death scythes
around the world.
Your point?
The point I'm making.
The point he's making here
is that we're going
to beat you
no matter what, right?
Hey, not cool, Stein.
That was my big line.
Medusa,
consider yourself fired.
Now.
Sutras go.
It's over.
You're not going
to get any closer
to me than that, professor.
Spectre plate!
What did you do?
Anything that's on top
of one of my vector plates
will be sent flying
in the direction
the arrow is pointing.
Of course,
the plates work on me
as easily as they do on you.
Spectre plate!
As you can imagine,
I'm not eager
to fight you up close anymore.
Dang, not again.
Now, come back this way.
Sutures.
You sewed your own body
to keep yourself in place.
But,
how can you fight this
when you're all sewn up?
Light servant!
Remove him.
Good one!
You timed that just right
so you could use
the plate to your advantage.
Vector, go!
Stein!
I have a thousand snakes
inside me
that are under my control.
They won't let any
easy prey like you escape.
Not eager to fight me
up close, yeah, right.
When you cause pain,
you love to see it up close.
Masquerading as a school nurse
was just another one
of your charades.
You're nothing but a liar.
I'm afraid you're wrong
about that.
Why don't you join me?
You remember that,
don't you,
while we were dancing?
I really meant
what I said at the party.
I'm not lying
when I say that I want you.
You're a scientist
just as I am.
We could watch
the world progress together.
What do you say,
Frankenstein?
Think about my offer.
I'm not asking you
as an instructor,
but as a man of science.
Hey,
what's wrong, Stein?
Vector plate.
Don't you see,
Professor Stein?
The vector plates
around you all point to me.
There's no point in resisting.
I always get what I want
in the end.
There is no escaping from me.
This isn't good.
We let someone get through
without even fighting.
We're gonna get in trouble again.
I can't deal with that.
Are you the demon sword?
Huh?
You don't look like
you can put up
a very good fight to me.
Defeating you
isn't gonna enhance
my reputation at all.
Seriously, dude,
you look pretty messed up.
Are you okay?
Oh, well,
who cares about you
and your problems anyway?
The important thing
is that I'm gonna
kick your ass.
Be careful, Blackstar.
Blackstar,
hold up a second.
You made it here quick
for someone so slow.
The sword.
Stand back
and let me handle this.
What?
Why?
What are you doing, Manka?
That's not the plan.
Professor Stein
wanted Blackstar
to take care
of the demon sword,
remember?
Listen to her.
She's right.
Our attacks don't work
against that thing.
What are you thinking?
I'm not gonna let you
take the spotlight off me.
Come on, now.
Keep acting cocky like this
and you're gonna
get yourself killed.
This is my chance
for revenge.
A good student
like you, Manka?
Disobeying a direct order
from a professor?
What?
Teen Rebellion?
Just stand back.
All right,
if that's how
you're gonna be.
Spotlight's yours.
Let's get started.
Yeah.
No, not permitted.
It's purple.
Is Rachel's mic
Nukic
A podría
Thank you.
I don't do anything ever
At this moment we can repeat
Our days will take me
Other days
So later
At this moment let's go
For kids to 하고
Boys & girls
There are negative existence
It's time for revenge. Let's go, Seoul.
Hey, what are you talking about? I'm Kid, not Seoul.
Don't worry. We're gonna make him pay for what he did to you, Seoul.
Didn't you hear me? I'm not Seoul.
I will get stronger.
Nope, still not Seoul.
Are you ready to do this, Seoul?
I'm not Seoul.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the Black Blood Resonance Battle,
a small soul's grand struggle against fear?
Watch it, or I'll take your Seoul.
I'm telling you, I'm not Kid.
Wait, no, that's not right.